<?xml version='1.0'?>
<stream>
    <message type="info">Loading repository data...</message>
    <message type="info">Reading installed packages...</message>
    <message type="info">Ignoring option --with-update when updating the update stack first.</message>
    <message type="info">Resolving package dependencies...</message>
    <install-summary download-size="14682713" space-usage-diff="70846" packages-to-change="11" need-restart="1"
                     need-reboot="0">
        <to-upgrade>
            <solvable type="package" name="python2-rpm" edition="4.14.3-150300.46.1" arch="x86_64"
                      repository="module_python2_update_repo" edition-old="4.14.1-29.2" arch-old="x86_64"
                      summary="Python Bindings for Manipulating RPM Packages">
                <description>This package contains a module that permits applications written in
                    the Python programming language to use the interface supplied by
                    RPM Package Manager libraries.

                    This package should be installed if you want to develop Python programs
                    that will manipulate RPM packages and databases.
                </description>
            </solvable>
            <solvable type="package" name="python3-distro" edition="1.5.0-3.5.1" arch="noarch"
                      repository="os_update_repo" edition-old="1.5.0-3.3.1" arch-old="noarch"
                      summary="Linux Distribution - a Linux OS platform information API">
                <description>distro (for: Linux Distribution) provides information about the Linux distribution it runs
                    on, such as a reliable machine-readable ID, or version information.

                    It is a renewed alternative implementation for Python&apos;s original platform.linux_distribution
                    function, but it also provides much more functionality which isn&apos;t necessarily Python bound
                    like a command-line interface.
                </description>
            </solvable>
            <solvable type="package" name="python3-rpm" edition="4.14.3-150300.46.1" arch="x86_64"
                      repository="os_update_repo" edition-old="4.14.1-29.2" arch-old="x86_64"
                      summary="Python Bindings for Manipulating RPM Packages">
                <description>This package contains a module that permits applications written in
                    the Python programming language to use the interface supplied by
                    RPM Package Manager libraries.

                    This package should be installed if you want to develop Python programs
                    that will manipulate RPM packages and databases.
                </description>
            </solvable>
            <solvable type="package" name="python3-salt" edition="3004-150300.53.24.1" arch="x86_64"
                      repository="os_update_repo" edition-old="3004-150300.53.21.1" arch-old="x86_64"
                      summary="python3 library for salt">
                <description>Python3 specific files for salt</description>
            </solvable>
            <solvable type="package" name="rpm" edition="4.14.3-150300.46.1" arch="x86_64" repository="os_update_repo"
                      edition-old="4.14.1-29.46" arch-old="x86_64" summary="The RPM Package Manager">
                <description>RPM Package Manager is the main tool for managing the software packages
                    of the SUSE Linux distribution.

                    RPM can be used to install and remove software packages. With rpm, it
                    is easy to update packages. RPM keeps track of all these manipulations
                    in a central database. This way it is possible to get an overview of
                    all installed packages. RPM also supports database queries.
                </description>
            </solvable>
            <solvable type="package" name="rpm-build" edition="4.14.3-150300.46.1" arch="x86_64"
                      repository="server_module_update_repo" edition-old="4.14.1-29.46" arch-old="x86_64"
                      summary="Tools and Scripts to create rpm packages">
                <description>If you want to build a rpm, you need this package. It provides rpmbuild
                    and requires some packages that are usually required.
                </description>
            </solvable>
            <solvable type="package" name="salt" edition="3004-150300.53.24.1" arch="x86_64" repository="os_update_repo"
                      edition-old="3004-150300.53.21.1" arch-old="x86_64" summary="A parallel remote execution system">
                <description>Salt is a distributed remote execution system used to execute commands and
                    query data. It was developed in order to bring the best solutions found in
                    the world of remote execution together and make them better, faster and more
                    malleable. Salt accomplishes this via its ability to handle larger loads of
                    information, and not just dozens, but hundreds or even thousands of individual
                    servers, handle them quickly and through a simple and manageable interface.
                </description>
            </solvable>
            <solvable type="package" name="salt-api" edition="3004-150300.53.24.1" arch="x86_64"
                      repository="module_server_applications_update_repo" edition-old="3004-150300.53.21.1"
                      arch-old="x86_64" summary="The api for Salt a parallel remote execution system">
                <description>salt-api is a modular interface on top of Salt that can provide a variety of entry points
                    into a running Salt system.
                </description>
            </solvable>
            <solvable type="package" name="salt-master" edition="3004-150300.53.24.1" arch="x86_64"
                      repository="module_server_applications_update_repo" edition-old="3004-150300.53.21.1"
                      arch-old="x86_64" summary="The management component of Saltstack with zmq protocol supported">
                <description>The Salt master is the central server to which all minions connect.
                    Enabled commands to remote systems to be called in parallel rather
                    than serially.
                </description>
            </solvable>
            <solvable type="package" name="salt-minion" edition="3004-150300.53.24.1" arch="x86_64"
                      repository="os_update_repo" edition-old="3004-150300.53.21.1" arch-old="x86_64"
                      summary="The client component for Saltstack">
                <description>Salt minion is queried and controlled from the master.
                    Listens to the salt master and execute the commands.
                </description>
            </solvable>
            <solvable type="package" name="zypper-needs-restarting" edition="1.14.52-150200.30.2" arch="noarch"
                      repository="os_update_repo" edition-old="1.14.43-3.20.1" arch-old="noarch"
                      summary="needs-restarting compatibility with zypper">
                <description>provides compatibility to YUM needs-restarting command using zypper</description>
            </solvable>
        </to-upgrade>
        <to-install>
            <solvable type="patch" name="SUSE-SLE-Module-Basesystem-15-SP3-2021-1833" edition="1" arch="noarch"
                      repository="os_update_repo" summary="Recommended update for zypper">
                <description>This update for zypper fixes the following issues:

                    zypper was upgraded to 1.14.44:

                    - man page: Recommend the needs-rebooting command to test whether a system reboot is suggested.
                    - patch: Let a patch&apos;s reboot-needed flag overrule included packages. (bsc#1183268)
                    - Quickfix setting &quot;openSUSE_Tumbleweed&quot; as default platform for &quot;MicroOS&quot;.
                    (bsc#1153687)
                    - Protect against strict/relaxed user umask via sudo. (bsc#1183589)
                    - xml summary: Add solvables repository alias. (bsc#1182372)

                    libzypp was upgraded from version 17.25.8 to version 17.25.10

                    - Properly handle permission denied when providing optional files. (bsc#1185239)
                    - Fix service detection with `cgroupv2`. (bsc#1184997)
                    - Add missing includes for GCC 11. (bsc#1181874)
                    - Fix unsafe usage of static in media verifier.
                    - `Solver`: Avoid segfault if no system is loaded. (bsc#1183628)
                    - `MediaVerifier`: Relax media set verification in case of a single not-volatile medium.
                    (bsc#1180851)
                    - Do no cleanup in custom cache dirs. (bsc#1182936)
                    - `ZConfig`: let `pubkeyCachePath` follow `repoCachePath`.
                </description>
            </solvable>
            <solvable type="patch" name="SUSE-SLE-Module-Basesystem-15-SP3-2021-1879" edition="1" arch="noarch"
                      repository="os_update_repo" summary="Recommended update for libzypp, zypper">
                <description>This update for libzypp, zypper fixes the following issues:

                    libzypp was updated to 17.26.0:

                    - Work around download.o.o broken https redirects.
                    - Allow trusted repos to add additional signing keys (bsc#1184326)
                    Repositories signed with a trusted gpg key may import additional
                    package signing keys. This is needed if different keys were used
                    to sign the the packages shipped by the repository.
                    - MediaCurl: Fix logging of redirects.
                    - Use 15.3 resolver problem and solution texts on all distros.
                    - $ZYPP_LOCK_TIMEOUT: Let negative values wait forever for the
                    zypp lock (bsc#1184399)
                    Helps boot time services like &apos;zypper purge-kernels&apos; to wait for
                    the zypp lock until other services using zypper have completed.
                    - Fix purge-kernels is broken in Leap 15.3 (bsc#1185325)
                    Leap 15.3 introduces a new kernel package called
                    kernel-flavour-extra, which contain kmp&apos;s. Currently kmp&apos;s are
                    detected by name &quot;.*-kmp(-.*)?&quot; but this does not work which
                    those new packages. This patch fixes the problem by checking
                    packages for kmod(*) and ksym(*) provides and only falls back to
                    name checking if the package in question does not provide one of
                    those.
                    - Introduce zypp-runpurge, a tool to run purge-kernels on
                    testcases.

                    zypper was updated to 1.14.45:

                    - Fix service detection with cgroupv2 (bsc#1184997)
                    - Add hints to &apos;trust GPG key&apos; prompt.
                    - Add report when receiving new package signing keys from a
                    trusted repo (bsc#1184326)
                    - Added translation using Weblate (Kabyle)
                </description>
            </solvable>
            <solvable type="patch" name="SUSE-SLE-Module-Basesystem-15-SP3-2021-2106" edition="1" arch="noarch"
                      repository="os_update_repo" summary="Security update for salt">
                <description>This update for salt fixes the following issues:

                    Update to Salt release version 3002.2 (jsc#ECO-3212, jsc#SLE-18033, jsc#SLE-18028)

                    - Check if dpkgnotify is executable (bsc#1186674)
                    - Drop support for Python2. Obsoletes `python2-salt` package (jsc#SLE-18028)
                    - virt module updates
                    * network: handle missing ipv4 netmask attribute
                    * more network support
                    * PCI/USB host devices passthrough support
                    - Set distro requirement to oldest supported version in requirements/base.txt
                    - Bring missing part of async batch implementation back (CVE-2021-25315, bsc#1182382)
                    - Always require `python3-distro` (bsc#1182293)
                    - Remove deprecated warning that breaks minion execution when &quot;server_id_use_crc&quot; opts is
                    missing
                    - Fix pkg states when DEB package has &quot;all&quot; arch
                    - Do not force beacons configuration to be a list.
                    - Remove msgpack &lt; 1.0.0 from base requirements (bsc#1176293)
                    - msgpack support for version &gt;= 1.0.0 (bsc#1171257)
                    - Fix issue parsing errors in ansiblegate state module
                    - Prevent command injection in the snapper module (bsc#1185281, CVE-2021-31607)
                    - transactional_update: detect recursion in the executor
                    - Add subpackage salt-transactional-update (jsc#SLE-18033)
                    - Improvements on &quot;ansiblegate&quot; module (bsc#1185092):
                    * New methods: ansible.targets / ansible.discover_playbooks
                    - Add support for Alibaba Cloud Linux 2 (Aliyun Linux)
                    - Regression fix of salt-ssh on processing targets
                    - Update target fix for salt-ssh and avoiding race condition on salt-ssh event processing
                    (bsc#1179831, bsc#1182281)
                    - Add notify beacon for Debian/Ubuntu systems
                    - Fix zmq bug that causes salt-call to freeze (bsc#1181368)
                </description>
            </solvable>
            <solvable type="patch" name="SUSE-SLE-Module-Basesystem-15-SP3-2021-2273" edition="1" arch="noarch"
                      repository="os_update_repo" summary="Recommended update for libzypp, zypper">
                <description>This update for libzypp, zypper fixes the following issues:

                    - Enhance XML output of repo GPG options
                    - Add optional attributes showing the raw values actually present in the &apos;.repo&apos; file.
                    - Link all executables with -PIE (bsc#1186447)
                    - Ship an empty &apos;/etc/zypp/needreboot&apos; per default (jsc#PM-2645)
                    - Add &apos;Solvable::isBlacklisted&apos; as superset of retracted and ptf packages (bsc#1186503)
                    - Fix segv if &apos;ZYPP_FULLOG&apos; is set.
                </description>
            </solvable>
            <solvable type="patch" name="SUSE-SLE-Module-Basesystem-15-SP3-2021-2682" edition="1" arch="noarch"
                      repository="os_update_repo" summary="Security update for rpm">
                <description>This update for rpm fixes the following issues:

                    - Changed default package verification level to &apos;none&apos; to be compatible to rpm-4.14.1
                    - Made illegal obsoletes a warning
                    - Fixed a potential access of freed mem in ndb&apos;s glue code (bsc#1179416)
                    - Added support for enforcing signature policy and payload verification step to
                    transactions (jsc#SLE-17817)
                    - Added :humansi and :hmaniec query formatters for human readable output
                    - Added query selectors for whatobsoletes and whatconflicts
                    - Added support for sorting caret higher than base version
                    - rpm does no longer require the signature header to be in a contiguous
                    region when signing (bsc#1181805)

                    Security fixes:

                    - CVE-2021-3421: A flaw was found in the RPM package in the read functionality. This flaw allows an
                    attacker who can convince a victim to install a seemingly verifiable package or compromise an RPM
                    repository, to cause RPM database corruption. The highest threat from this vulnerability is to
                    data integrity (bsc#1183543)

                    - CVE-2021-20271: A flaw was found in RPM&apos;s signature check functionality when reading a
                    package file.
                    This flaw allows an attacker who can convince a victim to install a seemingly verifiable package,
                    whose signature header was modified, to cause RPM database corruption and execute code. The highest
                    threat from this vulnerability is to data integrity, confidentiality, and system availability
                    (bsc#1183545)

                    - CVE-2021-20266: A flaw was found in RPM&apos;s hdrblobInit() in lib/header.c. This flaw allows an
                    attacker
                    who can modify the rpmdb to cause an out-of-bounds read. The highest threat from this vulnerability
                    is to system availability.
                </description>
            </solvable>
            <solvable type="patch" name="SUSE-SLE-Module-Basesystem-15-SP3-2021-3501" edition="1" arch="noarch"
                      repository="os_update_repo" summary="Recommended update for libzypp, zypper, libsolv, protobuf">
                <description>This update for libzypp, zypper, libsolv and protobuf fixes the following issues:

                    - Choice rules: treat orphaned packages as newest (bsc#1190465)
                    - Avoid calling &apos;su&apos; to detect a too restrictive sudo user umask (bsc#1186602)
                    - Do not check of signatures and keys two times(redundant) (bsc#1190059)
                    - Rephrase vendor conflict message in case 2 packages are involved (bsc#1187760)
                    - Show key fpr from signature when signature check fails (bsc#1187224)
                    - Fix solver jobs for PTFs (bsc#1186503)
                    - Fix purge-kernels fails (bsc#1187738)
                    - Fix obs:// platform guessing for Leap (bsc#1187425)
                    - Make sure to keep states alives while transitioning. (bsc#1190199)
                    - Manpage: Improve description about patch updates(bsc#1187466)
                    - Manpage: Recommend the needs-rebooting command to test whether a system reboot is suggested.
                    - Fix kernel-*-livepatch removal in purge-kernels. (bsc#1190815)
                    - Fix crashes in logging code when shutting down (bsc#1189031)
                    - Do not download full files even if the checkExistsOnly flag is set. (bsc#1190712)
                    - Add need reboot/restart hint to XML install summary (bsc#1188435)
                    - Prompt: choose exact match if prompt options are not prefix free (bsc#1188156)
                    - Include libprotobuf-lite20 in products to enable parallel downloads. (jsc#ECO-2911, jsc#SLE-16862)
                </description>
            </solvable>
            <solvable type="patch" name="SUSE-SLE-Module-Basesystem-15-SP3-2021-3870" edition="1" arch="noarch"
                      repository="os_update_repo" summary="Recommended update for libzypp, zypper">
                <description>This update for libzypp, zypper fixes the following issues:

                    libzypp:

                    - Check log writer before accessing it (bsc#1192337)
                    - Zypper should keep cached files if transaction is aborted (bsc#1190356)
                    - Require a minimum number of mirrors for multicurl (bsc#1191609)
                    - Fixed slowdowns when rlimit is too high by using procfs to detect niumber of
                    open file descriptors (bsc#1191324)
                    - Fixed zypper incomplete messages when using non English localization (bsc#1191370)
                    - RepoManager: Don&apos;t probe for plaindir repository if the URL schema is a plugin (bsc#1191286)
                    - Disable logger in the child process after fork (bsc#1192436)

                    zypper:

                    - Fixed Zypper removing a kernel explicitely pinned that uses uname -r output format as name
                    (openSUSE/zypper#418)

                </description>
            </solvable>
            <solvable type="patch" name="SUSE-SLE-Module-Basesystem-15-SP3-2022-1157" edition="1" arch="noarch"
                      repository="os_update_repo" summary="Security update for libsolv, libzypp, zypper">
                <description>This update for libsolv, libzypp, zypper fixes the following issues:

                    Security relevant fix:

                    - Harden package signature checks (bsc#1184501).

                    libsolv update to 0.7.22:

                    - reworked choice rule generation to cover more usecases
                    - support SOLVABLE_PREREQ_IGNOREINST in the ordering code (bsc#1196514)
                    - support parsing of Debian&apos;s Multi-Arch indicator
                    - fix segfault on conflict resolution when using bindings
                    - fix split provides not working if the update includes a forbidden vendor change
                    - support strict repository priorities
                    new solver flag: SOLVER_FLAG_STRICT_REPO_PRIORITY
                    - support zstd compressed control files in debian packages
                    - add an ifdef allowing to rename Solvable dependency members (&quot;requires&quot; is a keyword in
                    C++20)
                    - support setting/reading userdata in solv files
                    new functions: repowriter_set_userdata, solv_read_userdata
                    - support queying of the custom vendor check function
                    new function: pool_get_custom_vendorcheck
                    - support solv files with an idarray block
                    - allow accessing the toolversion at runtime

                    libzypp update to 17.30.0:

                    - ZConfig: Update solver settings if target changes (bsc#1196368)
                    - Fix possible hang in singletrans mode (bsc#1197134)
                    - Do 2 retries if mount is still busy.
                    - Fix package signature check (bsc#1184501)
                    Pay attention that header and payload are secured by a valid
                    signature and report more detailed which signature is missing.
                    - Retry umount if device is busy (bsc#1196061, closes #381)
                    A previously released ISO image may need a bit more time to
                    release it&apos;s loop device. So we wait a bit and retry.
                    - Fix serializing/deserializing type mismatch in zypp-rpm protocol (bsc#1196925)
                    - Fix handling of ISO media in releaseAll (bsc#1196061)
                    - Hint on common ptf resolver conflicts (bsc#1194848)
                    - Hint on ptf&lt;&gt;patch resolver conflicts (bsc#1194848)

                    zypper update to 1.14.52:

                    - info: print the packages upstream URL if available (fixes #426)
                    - info: Fix SEGV with not installed PTFs (bsc#1196317)
                    - Don&apos;t prevent less restrictive umasks (bsc#1195999)
                </description>
            </solvable>
            <solvable type="patch" name="SUSE-SLE-Module-Basesystem-15-SP3-2022-2178" edition="1" arch="noarch"
                      repository="os_update_repo" summary="Security update for salt">
                <description>This update for salt fixes the following issues:

                    - CVE-2022-22967: Fixed missing check for PAM_ACCT_MGM return value that could be used to bypass PAM
                    authentication (bsc#1200566)
                </description>
            </solvable>
            <solvable type="patch" name="SUSE-SLE-Module-Basesystem-15-SP3-2022-348" edition="1" arch="noarch"
                      repository="os_update_repo" summary="Recommended update for libzypp">
                <description>This update for libzypp fixes the following issues:

                    - RepoManager: remember execution errors in exception history (bsc#1193007)
                    - Fix exception handling when reading or writing credentials (bsc#1194898)
                    - Fix install path for parser (bsc#1194597)
                    - Fix Legacy include (bsc#1194597)
                    - Public header files on older distros must use c++11 (bsc#1194597)
                    - Use the default zypp.conf settings if no zypp.conf exists (bsc#1193488)
                    - Fix wrong encoding of URI compontents of ISO images (bsc#954813)
                    - When invoking 32bit mode in userland of an aarch64 kernel, handle armv8l as armv7hl compatible
                    - Introduce zypp-curl as a sublibrary for CURL related code
                    - zypp-rpm: Increase rpm loglevel if ZYPP_RPM_DEBUG is set
                    - Save all signatures associated with a public key in its PublicKeyData
                </description>
            </solvable>
            <solvable type="patch" name="SUSE-SLE-Module-Basesystem-15-SP3-2022-788" edition="1" arch="noarch"
                      repository="os_update_repo" summary="Recommended update for libzypp, zypper">
                <description>This update for libzypp, zypper fixes the following issues:

                    - Fix handling of redirected command in-/output (bsc#1195326)
                    This fixes delays at the end of zypper operations, where
                    zypper unintentionally waits for appdata plugin scripts to
                    complete.
                </description>
            </solvable>
            <solvable type="patch" name="SUSE-SLE-Module-Python2-15-SP3-2021-2682" edition="1" arch="noarch"
                      repository="module_python2_update_repo" summary="Security update for rpm">
                <description>This update for rpm fixes the following issues:

                    - Changed default package verification level to &apos;none&apos; to be compatible to rpm-4.14.1
                    - Made illegal obsoletes a warning
                    - Fixed a potential access of freed mem in ndb&apos;s glue code (bsc#1179416)
                    - Added support for enforcing signature policy and payload verification step to
                    transactions (jsc#SLE-17817)
                    - Added :humansi and :hmaniec query formatters for human readable output
                    - Added query selectors for whatobsoletes and whatconflicts
                    - Added support for sorting caret higher than base version
                    - rpm does no longer require the signature header to be in a contiguous
                    region when signing (bsc#1181805)

                    Security fixes:

                    - CVE-2021-3421: A flaw was found in the RPM package in the read functionality. This flaw allows an
                    attacker who can convince a victim to install a seemingly verifiable package or compromise an RPM
                    repository, to cause RPM database corruption. The highest threat from this vulnerability is to
                    data integrity (bsc#1183543)

                    - CVE-2021-20271: A flaw was found in RPM&apos;s signature check functionality when reading a
                    package file.
                    This flaw allows an attacker who can convince a victim to install a seemingly verifiable package,
                    whose signature header was modified, to cause RPM database corruption and execute code. The highest
                    threat from this vulnerability is to data integrity, confidentiality, and system availability
                    (bsc#1183545)

                    - CVE-2021-20266: A flaw was found in RPM&apos;s hdrblobInit() in lib/header.c. This flaw allows an
                    attacker
                    who can modify the rpmdb to cause an out-of-bounds read. The highest threat from this vulnerability
                    is to system availability.
                </description>
            </solvable>
            <solvable type="patch" name="SUSE-SLE-Module-Server-Applications-15-SP3-2022-2178" edition="1" arch="noarch"
                      repository="module_server_applications_update_repo" summary="Security update for salt">
                <description>This update for salt fixes the following issues:

                    - CVE-2022-22967: Fixed missing check for PAM_ACCT_MGM return value that could be used to bypass PAM
                    authentication (bsc#1200566)
                </description>
            </solvable>
            <solvable type="patch" name="SUSE-SLE-Module-SUSE-Manager-Server-4.2-2021-2682" edition="1" arch="noarch"
                      repository="server_module_update_repo" summary="Security update for rpm">
                <description>This update for rpm fixes the following issues:

                    - Changed default package verification level to &apos;none&apos; to be compatible to rpm-4.14.1
                    - Made illegal obsoletes a warning
                    - Fixed a potential access of freed mem in ndb&apos;s glue code (bsc#1179416)
                    - Added support for enforcing signature policy and payload verification step to
                    transactions (jsc#SLE-17817)
                    - Added :humansi and :hmaniec query formatters for human readable output
                    - Added query selectors for whatobsoletes and whatconflicts
                    - Added support for sorting caret higher than base version
                    - rpm does no longer require the signature header to be in a contiguous
                    region when signing (bsc#1181805)

                    Security fixes:

                    - CVE-2021-3421: A flaw was found in the RPM package in the read functionality. This flaw allows an
                    attacker who can convince a victim to install a seemingly verifiable package or compromise an RPM
                    repository, to cause RPM database corruption. The highest threat from this vulnerability is to
                    data integrity (bsc#1183543)

                    - CVE-2021-20271: A flaw was found in RPM&apos;s signature check functionality when reading a
                    package file.
                    This flaw allows an attacker who can convince a victim to install a seemingly verifiable package,
                    whose signature header was modified, to cause RPM database corruption and execute code. The highest
                    threat from this vulnerability is to data integrity, confidentiality, and system availability
                    (bsc#1183545)

                    - CVE-2021-20266: A flaw was found in RPM&apos;s hdrblobInit() in lib/header.c. This flaw allows an
                    attacker
                    who can modify the rpmdb to cause an out-of-bounds read. The highest threat from this vulnerability
                    is to system availability.
                </description>
            </solvable>
        </to-install>
    </install-summary>
    <prompt id="0">
        <text>Continue?</text>
        <option default="1" value="y"
                desc="Yes, accept the summary and proceed with installation/removal of packages."/>
        <option value="n" desc="No, cancel the operation."/>
        <option value="v" desc="Toggle display of package versions."/>
        <option value="a" desc="Toggle display of package architectures."/>
        <option value="r" desc="Toggle display of repositories from which the packages will be installed."/>
        <option value="m" desc="Toggle display of package vendor names."/>
        <option value="d" desc="Toggle between showing all details and as few details as possible."/>
        <option value="g" desc="View the summary in pager."/>
    </prompt>
